<resources>
    <string name="app_name">4Screens</string>
    <string name="hulk">HULK :</string>
    <string name="hulk1">The Hulk is a fictional superhero appearing in publications by the American publisher Marvel Comics. Created by writer Stan Lee and artist Jack Kirby, the character first appeared in the debut issue of The Incredible Hulk (May 1962). In his comic book appearances, the character is both the Hulk, a green-skinned, hulking and muscular humanoid possessing a vast degree of physical strength, and his alter ego Dr. Robert Bruce Banner, a physically weak, socially withdrawn, and emotionally reserved physicist. The two exist as independent dissociative personalities, and resent each other.</string>
    <string name="thor">Thanos is a fictional supervillain appearing in American comic books published by Marvel Comics. HAvengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.While usually portrayed as an evil-bent villain, many stories have alternatively depicted thanos as having a twisted moral compass and thinking of his actions as justified. The characters perhaps best-known role came in the 1991 storyline The Infinity Gauntlet, the culmination of several previous story arcs, which saw him successfully assembling the six Infinity Gems into a single gauntlet and using them to decimate half of the universe population, including many of its heroes, in an effort to earn the affection of Mistress Death, the living embodiment of death in the Marvel Universe. Although these events were later undone, the storyline has remained one of the most popular published by Marvel.</string>
    <string name="avengers">Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Mars superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.Avengers is a 2012 American superhero film based on the Marvel Comics superhero team of the same name.</string>
</resources>